Finally won at Plato's!
Correct!
Hello~~!
WOW!!!
So we are now at Tanabata Beach!
Now we are going to dive in like this!
It's est!
Fun!!!
I'm so excited, and the weather is very nice and it's a beautiful day at the beach, though,
This time, I'm going to make my long-time dream come true! This is a long time dream of mine is going to come true!
What? What? Dream come true? Tell me! What? What?
Let's see how well you can report on a paraglider!
Paragliding!
Yes!
Finally, paragliding!
I'm finally going to fulfill my dream of flying that I've been talking about for the past 3 or 4 years!
It's a reality moment!
It's great!
I can finally do it!
In the best location!
Super excited!
And what's more, this time I will be flying at 200m, but I have the option of doubling the altitude to 400m,
I'm going to try 400m even though it's my first time!
400m is amazing!
I wonder where it is?
Maybe you can't see it anymore!
It's amazing!
It's definitely a big sword!
And this time, we will have a paragliding report competition, and you can tell us who did the best report in the comments section, and the one with the most comments will win!
I see! So we're going to have a showdown!
It's important to know how well you can report in the sky, isn't it?
It's very important! Reporting skills are important!
I have to convey my excitement to those who are not flying,
I want to convey it!
I want to tell them!
By the way, do you fly high?
I can fly high,I can do high places though,
I'm not destructive to roller coasters and the like!
I'm not destructive!
I'm just devastatingly bad at it!
I see!
And you know, I'm actually planning on paragliding this time,
But we had to cancel it once,
Last time, it rained a little too hard and we had to cancel,
We had to change it to a sightseeing tour of Matsushima,
That was fun, too!
It was so much fun! I thought it was a trip!
Yes! It was a trip!
But you know, I was a little disappointed then, too,
I hope to be able to revenge that feeling as well,
Please check out the Matsushima sightseeing tour!
Please do!
So, this time, my dream will come true once again,
I really, really couldn't wait for today!
Yes!
I didn't sleep!
What?
You haven't slept?
I was really looking forward to it!
Yes! So, let's get ready to go!
Let's go!
This is the sitting equipment. It's called a harness.
That's what we're going to use.
We're going to put this on our backs.
Wow!
I'll get the landasel.
I'm going to lengthen it a little bit.
OK!
Now just put your helmet on and you're ready to go.
Okay, we'll do the helmets later.
Run into the wind.
I'm going to start up this paraglider over here.
Okay.I see.
There's a little bit of wind, so sometimes it pulls a little bit.
Sometimes it pulls like this.
You don't have to hold on so you don't fall.
Please follow me.
When you get to the top, I'll tell you to look ahead.
I'll tell you to look ahead.
The wind that says "look ahead" is this way.
Turn it this way.
And then we'll run.
I see.
Face forward.
When they tell you to look forward
I'll start running.
Yes, I understand.
That's how I feel.
Just keep running and running and running.
Before I knew it, my legs were like...
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee!
Until you leave
Run as far as you can.
Remember, the wind is good today, so you won't have to run that far.
When you first get in the air, you're still at a low altitude.
until you're at a safe enough altitude.
About 10 to 20 seconds.
When you stand up, I'll give you a signal... in my voice.
This is the voice that says, "Please sit down.
Sit down.
Yes, sir.
Then we go out to the sea.
We're going to go over the ocean for about 10 minutes, from 200 meters.
We're going to go up to 400 meters on the bio-range here.
Yes, sir.
And then we'll come back and we'll go down again.
When you get off, you have to sit down.
You can't stand up when you get off.
When we get into the landing gear...When we finally get into landing gear.
I'll say, "Okay, get ready to stand up.
And there's a belt right here.
There's a belt that goes to the paraglider.
So I'm going to hold it here, and I'm going to lean forward a little bit on my stomach.
I'll lean forward a little bit, and then I'll go back to the standing position.
and you'll be back to the initial standing position.
I'm going to hold this and then I'm going to do a little bit of this.
And then you can do a little bit of a wave.
I'm going to do this in the back, so it's totally
It's very easy.
Okay.
Let's go.
Have a good day.
Thank you for everything.
Thank you.
Have fun.
Best moment of your life.
Thank you.
Yes! Tachibana is ready!
Today is your first time paragliding.
We're going to have a report showdown in the sky.
Yuna-san is the queen of MC for Tohoku-san
I would like to give a shout out to Yuna-san... or should I say to Yuna-san...
I would like to fly as much as I can to show you the beauty of the sky.
I will fly as fast as I can.
I will do my best!
I'll do my best!
I'm off!
Bye!
Finally, Karen is flying!
That's great.
Let's go!
Bye!
I'm off!I'm off!
Whoa!
Whoo! Whoo!
Wow!
violorwhat
Looks like so much fun!
Karen, I was worried about you at first.
But it looks like you're having so much fun!
I'm glad she's having fun.
I was so scared that I told her that if she couldn't fly, I would fly twice.
But she did.
She's having so much fun.
Oh, she's looking at me.
Oh, you've got time, Karen.
Here's a celestial body.
The small mountain next to it is Mt.
JR East E233 series train
Ladies and gentlemen, we are now flying 400 meters in the air!
Wow! Wow!
It's amazing!
There are patterns on the sea, just like a map of Japan!
Wow! Wow!
That's amazing!
I was just told that Matsushima is over there.
I could see so many things!
I went to Matsushima the other day.
I could see many towers all over the place.
Since we are in the sky
I can see all of Japan.
Yay!
That's great!
Okay, let's take a look.
Now that we're in the sky
In the skyIn the sky
I'm gonna fly! I'd like to sing "I'm going to fly in the sky!
Please listen to it!
I'm gonna fly!
Higher and higher!
Aim high, aim high, aim high!
Jump-jump-jumper!
Jump up!
Yeah!
That's 200 meters.
The view is much different.
I think it's 400 meters.
It looks so low!
But it looks like a bird!
It's really the best one I've ever seen.
I've ever seen.
I've never seen anything like it.
Oh, my God!
We're flying through yesterday's rain!
Yesterday's rain is amazing!
Wow!
Yesterday's rain!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow!
Barrier!
Oh, my God!
I can see your head yesterday!
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
Wow!Wow!
Wow!
Yeah!
I'm home!
Welcome home.
Great, great, great, great, great, great.
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
Thank you.
Oh, my God. Your tone of voice and your face are so much brighter.
Really?
That's great. I bet you had a good time.
Welcome home.
I'm home.
That was awesome.
How was it?
I saw the world differently.
Really?
I've never seen anything like it.
It was amazing.
Did it feel good?
It felt good.
It was amazing. We didn't even get to the clouds, did we?
It was so close. I could see everything around here.
I could see all of Matsushima.
I could see Iwate Ku stadium.
I really felt like I was so small.
It was amazing, all my worries flew away.
This is amazing, Yuna!
I can fly!
I flew.
Really? I'm gonna make my dreams come true.Really? I'm gonna make my dream come true.
This is a dream come true. This is a dream come true.
Oh, my God.
You're more passionate than I am.
I'm telling you, I'm telling you, I'm telling you.
This is amazing.
That was amazing.
Oh, my God.
This one flew.
That's amazing.
Do you have any experience with flying?
Like this one?
Yeah, I guess so.
Is there anything I should do?
But, you know, you're going to hold the camera for me once.
I think it's better if you stretch your body as much as you can.
You'll feel the wind.
I feel like a bird.
And I don't know...
His voice is so funny.
And then, you know, when I get there, I can already feel the ocean.
You've inspired me to go there.
That was amazing.
I can feel it, from the heat of it.
You have to experience this.
Really? Oh, my God, I'm so excited.
Oh, my God.
Karen, I always thought it was great when you were flying.
Really?
I mean, today's the day.
I can fly.
That was amazing.
Was it the best day of your life?
No, it was, like, nothing compared to it.
Oh, really?
It's amazing. It's like, it's on a whole other level.
It was like a first.I feel like it's my first time.
It's the first time
I've never seen anything like it.
Really?
I didn't think it was human.
I was like...
What did you think it was?
I don't know. I thought it evolved into something non-human.
It was amazing. I don't think we ever saw anything like it.
Oh, my God.
I can't wait to fly.
I want it to fly.
That was amazing.
Seriously?
I think it's probably only run by parasites.
I know, right? How was the report?
I hope it was okay.
I don't give a shit about the report.
It's the ocean! It feels great! I was like, "It feels good!
Well, well, well.
That's a real report.
I want you to see my happy face.
I see.
That was amazing.
So, even if you're afraid of roller coasters, you can still go.
That's amazing.
You don't feel like you're floating?
It just felt really good.
I can't wait to go on it.
This is amazing.
Wow, clouds are beautiful!
Shall we go?
I'll be right back.
Okay, I'll be reporting next.
Go make your dreams come true.
Make your dream come true.
YunaimonYunaimon
Yunaimon!
Off you go!
Wow!
The day has finally come for you to make your dream come true!
I've been saying I wanted to fly for 3 or 4 years now.
Today I'm going to make it come true!
I'm very nervous, but
I'm so nervous, but I'd like to fly with the wind in my body
I would like to fly in the sky
I will share the excitement with you all!
I'm going to make my dream come true!
Wow! My dream is coming true!
I can fly!
Hey!
Oh, man.
I'm so excited.
I'm so happy, I can afford to be happy, my dream's gonna come true.
Oh, man! Oh, my God.
Thank you so much.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, I can't wait to find something this big.
Shall we go?
I'm off!
Bye!
Please, please, please.
Please, sir.
I'm gonna need you to turn your back on the pilot.
Let's go!
That's great.
I'm going to make my dream come true.
I'm gonna fly!
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Yes, sir.
I'm going.
All of it.All of it.
Here we go.
Yes, walking sideways!
Yes!
Yikes.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
That's hard to do.
Amazing!
That's great!
That's amazing!
I feel like popped Jingleinkles!Something already popped Jingleinkles!
popped Jingles!
JR East Japan E233 series train
JR East Japan Railway Series E233 Train
East Japan Railway Series E233
East Japan Railway Series E233 Train
This is my treasure for life!
This is my property.
No matter who or what steals my brain, they can't steal my brain, so they can't steal this for the rest of my life!
Amazing!
This is really amazing! Seeing this makes me feel like my daily life is so small!
This place is amazing!
The sky is wide, the sea is wide...
I'm... I'm... I'm...
I feel the wind, the earth, and the sky.
I'm really feeling it with my whole body.
Oh my gosh! This is bad!
This is really bad!
I'm really starting to cry!
Oh, my God!
This is really great!
Such a view!
There's more than this...
This is the normal 200m or so.
It's totally different from what we saw up there.
It looks so low, doesn't it?
I feel like I'm missing something.
The view at 400m is just too much.
It's amazing!
I know what you're going through right now.
All the things that are bothering you right now
Everything you're worried about
Will be solved.
How great is that?
It's amazing!Oh my God!
It's really pouring!
Everyone is here!
JR East E233 Series
East Japan Railway Series E233
East Japan Railway Series E233 Trains
I'm so happy!
That's great!
You look so happy!
Wow!
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you for this, too.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
That's great.
How was it?
Oh, I don't know.
It was great.
It was great!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I don't know!
It's really great!
I don't know what to do!
Leave all my vocabulary empty
Oh, my God!
It's amazing!Oh my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! I mean, we're flying.
I mean, it's not like the view is great.
I'm not talking about flying anymore.
I know what you're talking about! It's on a whole other level.
Oh, my God!
My dream came true!
That was amazing!
Oh, my God! This is amazing!
It's not just the scenery and the excitement.
I felt the universe and the earth.
I felt I was living on the earth.
I know!
Don't you live in Japan?
Don't you live in Sendai?
You live on Earth?
That's amazing!
Hey!
It's working.
That's great.
This is really great.
I wonder how long I'll have to wear the helmet.
I do, and my go-flow...
I'm sorry.
I've been wearing it all the way down...
We experienced paragliding this time, but they also do hot air ballooning.
And there's also Tico, the glass design studio where Waka and I experienced glass cup making.
There is also a glass design studio, Tico, and a soft-serve ice cream shop next to it.
And you know what, we got one too!
If you experience paragliding, you can get a 100 yen discount coupon for soft-serve ice cream!
This is amazing!
Such a great experience!
The soft serve ice cream after this experience is probably the best ice cream in the store!
You can't get better ice cream than this!
So I hope everyone will come and visit us for all kinds of things to do!
I hear it's open all the time from spring to fall.
So thank you very much for your time today!So thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
I hope you all will continue to support Ms. Inari Tohoku in the future.
Yuna Sasaki
Kae Tachibana
Kae Tachibana.
Isn't she so cute?
Oh, is it a video?
Hello.
Wow!
I'm so excited!
Oh, my God, it changed my life.
Really? That's great!
Yes, it is.
It's a dream come true.
Yes, it did.
It's beyond my wildest dreams.
It's gone beyond the level of what I thought it would be.
Hot, hot, hot.
I've definitely done it before.
I know, I know. What am I talking about?
I'm a beginner
It's okay, it's okay.
Thank you so much.
I knew it. It's so hot.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
It's good.
I knew it.
It's the best I've ever tasted.
It's so good!
Seriously delicious!
But it's probably the best I've ever tasted, whether I'm riding this glider or not.But this one probably, whether you're on this glider or not.
It's really good.
Oh, it's delicious.
It's like tiramisu.
That's genius. You're getting better at reporting.
It really is like tiramisu.
I'm an adult with a sweet tooth. It's definitely just right.
It's delicious.
Genius!
This time we were at Nana's soft serve ice cream store.
It's right next door to the one I had last time at Garance Design Studio Tico.
They have a lot of different kinds of soft serve.
You might like it.
We have a lot of different kinds of soft serve ice cream, so please come and try some!
We recommend
Vaisen Coffee!
It's so good!
That's why
Bye bye!
We hope you guys will come and visit us!
The most delicious item ever!
Taste it!